

PAUL M HERMAN

Sanford, FL 32771

(C) 407-414-5903 | pmherman85@icloud.com LinkedIn: http://linkedin.com/in/pmherman85 Github: https://github.com/pmherman

Professional SummaryAn organized, detail-oriented, and conscientious self-starter, able to strategize and prioritize effectively to accomplish multiple tasks and stay calm under pressure, while being an experienced supervisor and trainer; able to explain information clearly, recognize excellence in individuals, and inspire team members to achieve their potential while working toward common goals and grow within an organization.

Application's Built

SoundCheck

- Project Manager
 App is designed to load information from bands that will show local concert (if any), videos and images all in one
 - Worked on Front End Code Worked on creation of modal and Firebase integration.
 - Merging code to GitHub
 - Development YouTube API integration

Professional Experience

Store Manager

Walgreens Boots Alliance

Mar 2014 - Current Longwood, FL

- Worked with over 100 Assistant Store Manager Trainees and Shift Leads to achieve new leadership for company.
- Analyzed department documents for appropriate distribution and filing.
- Obtained documents, clearances, certificates and approvals from local, state and federal agencies.
- Managed high volume pharmacy
- Increased store income by \$300,000 YoY
- Increased store level engagement and performance.
- Analyze business statements to create effective business plans to improve store performance and customer
- Payroll management, scheduling, cash management, merchandising, time management.
- Managed both hourly and overtime exempt employees, between 25 50 employees at one time.

Assistant Store Manager/Executive Asst. Manager

Walgreens Boots Alliance

Trained and promoted several Shift Leads

- · Coached and grew team members
- Improved performance at high volume 24 hour locations.

Drug Store Management Trainee

Walgreens Boots Alliance

Various other positions within the company since 2003: Service Clerk, Photo/Head Photo Specialist

Apr 2003 - May 2010

May 2010 - Mar 2014

Orlando, FL

Orlando, FL

Education

Full Stack Coding Boot Camp

University of Central Florida

2018 Sanford, FL

Bachelor of Science: Information Technology

University of Phoenix

 Coursework includes speech & communication, information technology with specialization in business and networking.

2016

Orlando, FL

Certified Pharmacy Technician

Pharmacy Technician Certification Board

2012 (Current and Active)

Registered Pharmacy Technician

Florida Department of Health

2010 (Current and Active)

Volunteer Organizations

- Nathaniel's Hope
- American Heart Association

- City of Longwood
- GR8TODON8 Organ Donation

Skills

- Process implementation
- Staff development
- Large computer networks
- Retail pharmacy operations knowledge

- Pharmacy automation
- Typing speed 100 WPM
- Regional level facilitation, coaching and training
- Peer development

- Networking within communities for community events, brand awareness, and volunteering
 Knowledgable with Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Premiere, Indesign)
 Knowledgable with Macintosh and Windows based systems
 Proficient with Microsoft Word, PowerPoint, Excel and Access
 HTML5, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, AJAX, Firebase, PHP, SQL
 Firebase